刑法により禁じられた犯罪行為＞
＜５年以下の懲役 または➡
50万円以下の
罰金に処せられます＞
＜後悔しても 元には戻せない＞
不正視聴!?
i realise the screaming pain
hearing loud in my brain
but i'm going straight ahead with the scar
I should just get over it and I should just stop feeling it
wasurete shimaeba ii yo kanjinaku nacchaeba ii
and so I covered my grazed heart
surimuita kokoro ni futa wo shitan da
I don't care if I'm hurt 'cause I don't feel pain anymore
kizutsuitatte heki da yo mou itami wa nai kara ne
all while you limped on while dragging your feet behind you
sono ashi wo hikizuri nagara mo
I had lost sight of myself
miushinatta jibun jishin ga
which had crumbled loudly to the ground
oto wo taete kuzureteita
but then I realised it was just the sound of the wind...
kizukeba kaze no oto dake ga
I came here to tell you something following my deep scars
tsutae ni kita yo kizuato wo tadotte
before I am completely crushed by this vast world
sekai ni oshitsubusarete shimau mae ni
do you remember that sky of tears
oboeteru kana namida no sora wo
that pain protected you for me
ano itami ga kimi no koto wo mamotte kureta
that pain is always protecting you
sono itami ga itsumo kimi wo mamotterunda
can you hear me so am i
The Forbidden
Jutsu Released
(シラナミ)隠された禁術を
探したところで➡
No wonder it was useless looking
for the Forbidden Jutsu.
見つからないわけだ。
自分の孫を器として
埋め込んでいたのだからな。
"CONTROL"
He had used his own granddaughter
as its hiding place.
役行者も
むごいことをするじゃねえか。
That En no Gyoja...
What a cruel thing to do.
器にされた人間から
禁術を取り出せば➡
If the Forbidden Jutsu is removed
from its human vessel,
術は 永遠に失われる。
it would become lost forever.
また 器となった人間が➡
And unless the human who became
its vessel is skilled enough to control it,
禁術を扱うレベルに
達していなければ➡
禁術自体が発動することはない。
the Forbidden Jutsu cannot be activated...
クッ… これならば➡
So even if someone were to come
after the Forbidden Jutsu,
禁術を狙う者が現れようと
コイツには手を出せない。
they cannot lay a hand on it.
役行者の優しさによって
守られていたというわけだ。
En no Gyoja's kindness has protected it.
だが このままじゃ
宝の持ち腐れだ。
However, if it stays this way,
the treasure will be wasted.
今のお前は 自然エネルギーを
ただ吸い込み 集める➡
Right now, you are no more than
a storage tank accumulating natural energy.
貯水タンクにしかすぎない。
その集めた自然エネルギーに➡
You have yet to wield the activation jutsu
necessary to
発動をうながす術を
持ち合わせていないからな。
set off that collected natural energy.
そこに現れたのが このオレ。
And then I come along...
発動の術を扱える
土蜘蛛一族 唯一の生き残り。
The sole survivor of the Tsuchigumo Clan
who has mastered that jutsu.
よかったな ホタル。
What a lucky turn of events, right Hotaru?
一族復興の希望 この術が➡
The jutsu which will restore the clan
to its glory
再び 日の目を浴びようと
しているんだぜ。
is on the verge of
seeing the light of day.
コイツで 一族をおとしめた連中に➡
Let's use it to give a scare to those
who denounced our clan.
ひと泡ふかせてやろうじゃないか。
ハハハハ。 なんだよ ホタル 嬉しいだろ？
What is it, Hotaru?
Aren't you happy?
だったら笑えよ。 なぁ よう！
Then laugh. Come on.
そうか お前も嬉しいか！
そうだろう？
I see.
You're happy too? You should be.
そうだろう？ ハハハハハ！
You should be.
土蜘蛛流禁制術解法。
Tsuchigumo Style:
Forbidden Jutsu Release!
天地開闢！
Big Bang!
きたきた！
It's coming... It's coming...
さぁ 一族再興の切り札 禁術が➡
Now, the trump card to our clan's revival...
十数年ぶりに目覚めるときがきた。
The moment is here...
The Forbidden Jutsu shall awaken
after its decade-long seal!
集え チャクラよ！
Gather chakra!
器たるホタルの体を満たせ！
Overflow in Hotaru's body,
which serves as the vessel!
そして
その大いなる力を見せてみろ！
And manifest your formidable power!
(ナルト)ウタカタ 何してるんだ？
Utakata! What are you doing?!
(ウタカタ)チャクラが流れている。
Chakra is flowing...
チャクラが？
Chakra?
んなもん見えねえってばよ。
I don't see anything.
おそらくは
自然界に存在するチャクラだ。
It is probably chakra that exists
within the atmosphere and terrain.
なんだ こりゃ…。
チャクラに…。
What is this?
They're riding the chakra,
チャクラの流れに乗って
一箇所へ向かっている。
the chakra's current,
towards a certain location.
そこに ホタルが…。
いるってのか？
And Hotaru is...
She's there?!
行くぞ！
Let's go!
お… おう！
Right!
なんで チャクラが集まってるんだ？
Why is the chakra gathering there?
なぁ？ 本当にホタルは
そこにいるんだろうな？
Hey, you're sure Hotaru will be there?
口を動かすヒマがあったら
足を動かせ。
If you have time to talk,
then get moving.
《ホタル…》
Hotaru...
あそこだ。
よっしゃ。
Over there!
All right!
ホタル！
Hotaru!
遅かったか…。
We're too late...
ちぇっ… 使えねえ連中だな。
Useless bunch.
もう少し 足止め
できなかったもんかね。
Couldn't they at least hold you off
a little longer?
まぁ ギャラリーは
多いほうがいいが…。
Oh well, I don't mind having
an audience.
テメエ… ホタルに何をした!?
You bastard!
What did you do to Hotaru?!
《ホタル : ウタカタ様…》
Utakata-sama...
ホタルの… コイツの望みを
叶えてやろうとしているんだよ。
Hotaru's dream...
I'm just helping her to realize it.
土蜘蛛一族の復興…
そのカギ 禁術を➡
The revival of the Tsuchigumo Clan.
And the key to that is
オレの手によって
解放してやろうとな。
activating the Forbidden Jutsu
with my abilities.
お前の手によって…
どういうことだ？
Your ability? What do you mean?
コイツには まだ
禁術を発動するスキルはない。
She doesn't have the skill to
activate the Forbidden Jutsu yet.
自然チャクラを
集める能力しかないのさ。
She's only able to accumulate
the chakra in nature.
そこで このオレが外から禁術を
発動させてやろうってわけだ。
So I'll activate it for her,
from the outside.
血にまみれた土蜘蛛一族の
プライドを取り戻すために。
In order to restore the tarnished honor
of the Tsuchigumo Clan.
何が プライドだ！
ホタルが大切にしていた➡
What honor?! All you're trying to do
is steal Hotaru's feelings
ホタルのじいさん 遁兵衛さん。
一族の思い！
for her grandfather, Tonbei-san,
and her people.
それを
盗もうとしてるだけじゃねえか！
Everything that Hotaru holds dear!
フッフッフ… 思いなんて
チンケなものはいらねえ。
Who needs something
as cheap as feelings?
オレは世界を盗む。
I'm going to steal the world.
なんだと!?
これさえあれば➡
What?!
As long as I have this, be it
the five Kage's or the Lords...
五影だろうが 大名だろうが➡
オレの言動を
無視することはできなくなる。
No one will be able to ignore me.
新たな里を… いや。
A new village...
五大国にも劣らぬ国でさえ
この手にすることができるんだ。
No, I can even attain lands
superior to the Five Great Nations.
キサマ 正気か!?
Are you out of your mind?!
正気も正気。
I've never been more serious.
ここまでくれば
十分 五大国とも戦える。
Now that I've come this far,
I can take on the Five Great Nations.
この禁術で 世界を
かっさらうことも夢じゃない！
With this Forbidden Jutsu,
taking over the world is
not just a dream!
やっぱり そうかよ！
お前にとっちゃ この里…。
I knew it!
You don't give a damn...
about the people of the Tsuchigumo Clan!
土蜘蛛一族のことなんて
どうでもいいってことか！
あぁ… 当然だろ。
Yeah... that goes without saying.
ホタルの… ホタルの気持は
どうしてくれんだよ！
What about...
What about Hotaru's feelings?!
知るか んなもん…。
(ウタカタ)お前に託したんだ…。
As if I care.
She put her faith in you...
あれほどの刻印を刻まれながら…。
A carved seal of that magnitude
was embedded into her...
守り抜いてきた禁術を…
里の復興のために…。
and she protected that
Forbidden Jutsu with all her might...
for the sake of her people.
ホタルは お前に託した。
And she entrusted you with it.
はぁ？
Huh?
ハッハッハ…
確かに オレは自分の欲のために➡
It's true that I killed my own father
in order to satisfy my greed.
父親をも
この手にかけた男だけどなぁ。
アンタが言うか？
知ってるんだぜ オレは…。
But you're not one to talk.
I know all about you.
ビンゴブックにも載っているよな アンタ。
You're listed in the Bingo Book,
aren't you?
霧隠れの抜け忍なんだろう？
You're a Rogue Ninja from
the Hidden Mist, right?
お前だって
霧隠れを捨てたんだろうが。
You turned your back on
the Hidden Mist.
里のことなんて思っちゃいない
お前に➡
I don't need to be lectured
by someone...
そんなことを言われたくない。
who doesn't care about his village!
へっ オレはな
感じるんだ お前から。
I can tell we're alike, you and I.
We smell the same!
このオレと同じ匂いをよ。
((騙しちゃいねえ
さっきの話は本当だ。
I didn't trick you.
What I told you earlier is true.
１つ補足しておくなら➡
Although I should add that my old man,
禁術を守って死んだ
親父を殺したのがオレだってことさ。
who died protecting
the Forbidden Jutsu,
was actually killed by me!
ヤツは師匠殺しのウタカタ。
Utakata is a heinous criminal
(里を抜けた大罪人だ))
who killed his master and
escaped from the village.
《違う。
No... Utakata-sama is nothing like this man!
ウタカタ様は こんな男とは違う。
なのに なのに 私は…！》
And yet, and yet I...
((うわ～！
うわぁ～!!
(ハルサメ)なに!?
What?!
これは これは… この力は…。
Th-This... power...
(止まれ 止まれ!!))
Wait! Stop! Stop!
図星なんだろう？
Did I hit it right on the mark?
ハハハ… まぁ どうでもいいことよ。
Well, whatever.
ホタルが それほどまでに
一族に こだわるというのなら➡
But since Hotaru is
so attached to her people,
オレ様の国を
土蜘蛛と名づけたっていいんだ。
I'm willing to name my new nation
after the Tsuchigumo.
やっぱ 盗人じゃない
生まれ育った一族を思い➡
I'm not a bandit, after all.
Thinking of the land of my birth,
復興に身を賭す。
I'm helping to bring it back to glory.
立派な善人じゃねえか。
ふざけるな！
I'd say I'm a pretty fine person!
Don't kid around!
確かに オレにとっては
どうでもいいことかもしれんな。
You're right.
Maybe I don't give a damn...
里のことなど。
ウタカタ！
about my village...
Utakata...
だが ホタルはどうなる!?
But what will happen to Hotaru?
生きるさ。
She'll live. As the ultimate weapon
for the Forbidden Jutsu.
禁術という最大の兵器として。
偉大なる術をおさめる➡
I will control this great jutsu...
オレの器としてな。
and she will be my tool.
器…。
Tool... Did you say "tool"?!
器と言ったのか!?
そうだ 器だ！
Yes...
My tool!
うるせえ！
Shut up!
"CONTROL"
残念だったな
もう お前はオレには逆らえない。
Too bad. You can't oppose me anymore.
ホタル同様にな。
Just like Hotaru.
いいぞ もっとだ。
Good... More...
その身をチャクラで埋め尽くせ！
Let your body overflow with chakra!
さてと お前には
何をやってもらおうか。
Now then, what shall
I make you do?
そうだな。
味方どうし
やりあうっていうのは どうだ？
How about making comrades
fight each other?
《動けねえ！》
I can't move...
それとも警護でもしてもらおうか。
Or maybe bodyguards?
オレの器の警護をな。
You can guard my tool.
コイツ…。
Why you...
"CONTROL"
そう簡単に
オレの器に近づけると思うな。
Don't think you can get near
my tool so easily.
器って言うんじゃねえ！
Don't call her your tool...
ホタルは器なんかじゃねえ！
Hotaru is not a tool!
しゃべるな！ うるせえ!!
Don't talk. You're irritating.
やめておけ。 お前たちに
言われる筋合いはない。
Forget it.
You have no grounds to object.
ホタルは このオレを選んだ。
Hotaru chose me.
She chose to become the vessel.
器になる道を
自ら望んだんだ。
((「私は シラナミ様と
土蜘蛛一族再興を目指します。
To Utakata-sama,
I will work to revive the Tsuchigumo Clan
with Shiranami-sama.
これまで
ありがとうございました。
Thank you for all you have done.
(さようなら。
弟子のホタルより」))
Good-bye...
From your student, Hotaru.
ホタルは お前らの助けなんて
望んじゃいないんだ。
Hotaru doesn't want
to be rescued by you.
そこで おとなしく土蜘蛛の里が
一瞬で消えるところを見てろ。
So stay there and watch as the Tsuchigumo
village disappears in an instant.
《ウタカタ様… ごめんなさい。
Utakata-sama. I'm so sorry.
私が 浅はかだったばかりに》
It's all because I was so foolish...
ほう… まだ
抗う心があるとはな。
Hmm... You still have the will to resist.
《ウタカタ様…》
くそっ…。
Utakata-sama.
Damn it!
あと少し。
あと少しで ホタルの器は
チャクラでいっぱいになる。
Just a little more... Just a little more
and Hotaru's vessel will be full of chakra.
お前たちには 禁術復活の
目撃者になってもらおう。
You will be my witnesses to
the resurrection of the Forbidden Jutsu.
(サクラ)これじゃあ まともに
あの４人と戦えない。
There's no way we can put up
a fight against those four like this.
(ヤマト)まずは 里の人たちの
足を止めないとね。
First, we have to stop the villagers.
(サイ)どうやって？
多少 荒っぽくなっても
しかたないでしょ。
But how?
It can't be helped if we get
a bit rough with them.
一箇所に集めて
隔離するよ。
We'll isolate them all in one place.
ごめんなさい。
ホントに 荒っぽくいくから。
I'm sorry!
しゃ～んなろ!!
I have to get a little rough.
Shannaro!
超獣偽画！
Super Beast Scroll!
おりゃあ!!
木遁 四柱牢の術！
Wood Style! Four Pillar House Jutsu!
しばらくは そこで
おとなしくしていてもらうよ。
We'll have them lay low there
for a while.
(ベンテン)あ～あ シラけるな。
Way to ruin our fun.
(アカボシ)しかし これ以上 自由に
させとくわけにはいかん。
We can't keep letting them
have their way.
それは こちらのセリフだよ。
That's our line.
それはどうかな？
I wonder about that.
(チュウシン)観客がいなきゃ
盛り上がらないんじゃねえの？
It's no fun... without an audience.
やれやれ…
ホント きりがないね。
Oh boy...
There's just no end to this, is there?
くそっ…。
Damn it...
いいぞ ホタル。
そろそろ お客さんも
お待ちかねだろうからな。
You're doing well, Hotaru.
Our guests are probably
getting anxious.
クッ！
あとは このオレに
身も心も預けろ。
Now surrender
your body and soul to me!
集めたチャクラを
一気に解き放つのだ。
Unleash the chakra you've
accumulated all at once!
お前を拒絶した この地を
焼き払ってやろうじゃないか!!
This place which rejected you...
Let's reduce it into ashes!
忍法…！
なにっ!?
起爆砲!!
Ninja Art...
What?!
うわぁ～っ!!
Bubble Bomb!
木偶が！
いつのまに こんな仕掛けを！
You blockhead!
おとなしくしていれば
もう少しだけ 長生きできたのに！
When did you set that up?
If you had behaved,
you could've lived a bit longer.
クッ！ ぐわぁ～っ!!
うぉ～っ!!
ど… どうして… 字縛術が!?
Why did my Wordbind Jutsu...?
コイツら
尋常じゃないチャクラの量を…！
These guys...
テメエなんかに➡
The amount of chakra is unnatural...
早々 操られて
たまるかってんだよ！
Like we'd let you control us so easily!
そうはさせるか～!!
I won't let you!
多重 影分身の術！
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
字縛術！ 岩！
Wordbind Jutsu!
岩!!
Rock!
この野郎!!
ぐわ～っ!!
You bastard!
ホタル！
大丈夫か!? ホタル！
Hotaru...
Are you all right, Hotaru?!
うっ… うっ… うっ…。
ホタル！
Hotaru!
どうすりゃいいんだよ!?
フッフッフッフッフッ！
テメエ！ まだ やるってのか!!
What do we do?
お～っと。 ホタルは 字縛術で➡
Why you... You still wanna fight?
Whoa!
操られているってことを
忘れたか？
Have you forgotten that
my Wordbind Jutsu controls Hotaru?
なっ…！
下がれ!!
クソッ！
自然チャクラの充填は➡
Get back!
Damn!
まだ 十分ではないが…。
She isn't fully charged with
the chakra from nature, but...
さぁ ホタル 見せてやろう。
Now Hotaru... Let us show them.
禁術の恐ろしさを…。
How dreadful
the Forbidden Jutsu is!
さぁ… 始めよう。
Now let us start.
《イヤ…》
No.
天下に知らしめよ！
オレたちの！
Let us show the world!
いや… オレ様の力を!!
Our...
No, my... power!
《イヤ…。 イヤ…》
No... No!
くたばれ!! 怒髪天!!
Die!
Fury Jutsu!
イヤ～!!
No!
here are the answers of the path
koko ni aru no wa kimi ga ima made erande michi no
you chose up till now, look and go on by yourself
kotae tachi yo hora jishin motte susumeba ii
it's very natural, like a rainbow over
totemo shizen na no amaeagari no
asphalt after a rainfall
asufaruto ni niji ga kakaru you ni
a lonely wind blew and
lonely kaze ga fuite
a feeling dawned on me
feeling ki ga tsuita yo
there are any answers anywhere
kotae wo doko ni mo nai kedo
call me, I got it already
call me wakatteru wa
with you, we'll always
with you ai wa itsu mo
love each other
atae au mono
for you
I'm sure one day you will
kitto kimi wa itsu no hi ka
be able to fly in the sky
kono sora wo toberu hazu dakara
no matter how many times we've stumbled for you
nando tsumaizuta to shite mo for you
there's only one thing important
taisetsu na koto wa hitotsu
which is to dream
yumemiru koto
so at least keep your heart open
kokoro dake wa tozasanaide ite
(ナツ)ゴチャゴチャ うるせえっての！
Next Episode
(グレイ)ナツ！
(ウェンディ)ナツさん！
I didn't want to hurt anybody.
(グレイ)野郎！
(ウェンディ)よくもナツさんを！
I wanted to protect this jutsu
entrusted by my grandfather
and carry out his dream.
(サミュエル)手順どおり。
And yet, I hurt Naruto-san and Utakata-sama
with my very own hands!
(ハッピー)ナツ 大丈夫？
(ナツ)あんにゃろう！
ちょっと待て！
I don't want it.
I betrayed Utakata-sama.
Someone like me should disappear
along with the Forbidden Jutsu!
Next time on Naruto Shippuden: "Master and Student"
Master
and
Student
Goodbye, Utakata-sama...